soft4phone.com 2017-12-07

# Slovoed

### General Provisions

This Privacy Policy applies to the entire business relationship between Paragon Software GmbH, Wiesentalstraße 22, D-79115, Freiburg, (also hereinafter referred to as ‘we’ or ‘us’) and our visitors (hereinafter referred to as "Users"). This document explains what information we collect about Users of this online resource and how we use this information. The privacy of those who visit this online resource is important to us. We support the goals and guidelines set forth by oversight laws and organizations devoted to providing online safety and privacy for children, households, parents and schools. We design and operate our technology and services with our Users’ protection and privacy in mind. For purposes of this Policy, personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person including e-mail, name, etc.

### Security Policy

Paragon Software GmbH takes the security of your personal information seriously. The online services protect your personal information during transit using encryption. When your personal data is stored, we use computer systems with limited access housed in facilities using physical security measures.

### Privacy Policy

Paragon Software GmbH guarantees to keep confidential all the information you provide and items we discussed. We are committed to protecting your privacy and we will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully in accordance with German and European Data Protection Laws. We collect information about you for two reasons: first to process your order and second to provide you with the best possible service. We will not email you in the future unless you have given your consent. The type of information we will collect about you after submitting the order form includes your name, address, phone number and email address. You can check the information hold by us about you by entering Slovoed Customer Service System at my.slovoed.com using your password and login we sent to you. If you find any inaccuracies, you will able to correct it promptly. We never pass on customer details to other companies or organizations for any purpose.

### Privacy Policy for apps

Paragon Software GmbH, Wiesentalstraße 22, D-79115, Freiburg, develops apps for Android, macOS, Windows, and other popular platforms. We integrate Google Analytics/Firebase service to our apps because we want our app user experience to be easy and seamless. These analytical services include, but are not limited to, Google Analytics SDK, Firebase SDK, and Fabric, depending on the platform.

Using these frameworks in our apps helps track purchases/refunds, conversion rates, and online sources where our customers come from, without collecting any information that personally identifies users, such as name, email address, IP address, phone, or other personal information that could be used to contact users or identifies who they are.

To provide users with a free trial period our Android apps collect Google IDs and Facebook IDs to bind the trial license to it. This data is securely transferred to our protected server and is stored encrypted without any access from third parties. This is required to provide trial access. We do not share this information with any third parties.

If you do not want these analytical services tracking your behavior while using Paragon Software product, you can disable this option in the product settings.

### PenReader handwriting recognition app

PenReader app converts any text (whether written with a finger or stylus) into printed one with the highest accuracy and speed. The app neither collects nor saves the information entered with a finger or stylus; it only saves the words added to the custom dictionary. We do not use the information added to the custom dictionary and do not share this information with any third parties.

### Cookies

The Users’ browser may save cookies while they are using our website. The use of our website means that the Users agree to this procedure.

**This is how we use cookies:**   
A cookie is a short text snippet, which is sent to the browser by a website the Users visited. It saves the Users’ information such as the last visit, the preferred language, or other settings. This will help Users find the way around our website quicker and use it more effectively the next time they access it. Cookies play an important role. Surfing the net would be frustrating without them. Cookies can also be used to analyze website use on our pages. This helps us optimize our website and deliver the relevant content in a target-oriented manner.   
**This is how we don’t use cookies:**   
We do not use cookies on our websites to collect personal or personalized data.    
**Cookie management**   
Most modern browsers allow Users to manage cookies as they please. Many browsers give the chance to set rules, which they can use to manage cookies for each individual website. This way, Users can rule out cookies from all websites, which they don’t trust. As an alternative, they can also deactivate the use of cookies on the browser entirely and thus prevent them from being used all together. 

### Data collection

Paragon Software GmbH processes Users’ information for the purpose of dealing with inquiries and for maintaining existing relations. Personal information about the Users will not be used for any purpose, which is unrelated to the use of the services unless specifically authorized by the Use

### Legally Required Disclosure and Transfer in a Corporate Transaction

We reserve the right to disclose the Users’ personal information if we are required to do so by law or if we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process. We also reserve the rights to transfer the personal information in case of a corporate restructuring (such as a merger or acquisition) as long as the receiving entity adopts this or stricter privacy policy that applies to the User’s information.

### Changes to this policy:

We constantly strive to provide the best products and services. As the Internet is a dynamic and ever changing medium and as new or changed products and services are released and threats and technologies evolve, changes to this policy may be required. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be cases where changes may be more significant, and in such cases we will first provide prominent notice to Users who are affected by such changes. We urge Users to examine this policy for changes when using this site. Posting the modified Privacy Policy on www.slovoed.com online resources will give effect to the revised terms. The continued use of this online resource indicates Users’ acceptance of any revised terms. If a User does not agree to the revised policy, we recommend refraining from using this online resource and/or leave this online resource. 

### Concluding provisions

The invalidity of individual provisions shall not affect the validity of the remaining Privacy Policy. In the case of contracts with traders, trading companies, public authorities, publicly-owned corporations and where the User, not being a consumer, is subject to a general jurisdiction outside this country, it is agreed that the court with jurisdiction shall be Freiburg im Breisgau. The German law applies.

### Contact us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or website practices, please contact us at [support@slovoed.com](mailto:support@slovoed.com)
